incentivelogic.com 2013-05-15

# Privacy Policy: Incentive Logic

**The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is May, 2012**

Welcome to the Incentive Logic Internet site (this "Site"), owned and operated by Incentive Logic, Inc. (“Incentive Logic”, “our”, “us” or “we”) and located at the URL; [www.incentivelogic.com](http://www.incentivelogic.com/). Incentive Logic wants you to know what information we learn about you when you visit this Site, what we do with that information and any other information you voluntarily provide us through this Site or by other means and how you can view or change the information we have. This privacy policy describes our information collection and use practices on this Site. It does not apply to information you might provide on another site operated by us, or one of our partners or affiliates, nor does it apply to information you may provide to us through other forums, including offline or through electronic mail.

Incentive Logic Inc. complies with the U.S. – E.U. & U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union and Switzerland. Information regarding the U.S. - E.U. & U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor Framework can be found at: <http://export.gov/safeharbor>.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please email us at [info@incentivelogic.com](mailto:info@incentivelogic.com) or through one of the means provided in the Contact Us section below.

**Notice to California Residents / Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents who have supplied personal information, as defined in the statute, to the Site to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes (namely, the categories of personal information shared and the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information from this Site for their direct marketing purposes) during the immediately prior calendar year (for example, requests made in 2011 will receive information about 2010 sharing activities). To make such a request (limit one request per year), please send an e-mail to [info@incentivelogic.com](mailto:info@incentivelogic.com), with “California Privacy Rights” as the subject line. You must include your full name, e-mail address, and postal address in your message.

**Information Collected At This Site**

There are two types of information that we can learn about you as you browse and use this site. Each type of information can be used in a different way: 1. Internet-related Information - generic statistical and demographic information that we gather passively from visitors to the Site; and 2. Personal Information that you provide when making contact with us.

The Site is not directed to children younger than thirteen (13), and Incentive Logic does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children younger than thirteen (13). If Incentive Logic discovers that a person younger than thirteen (13), has provided the Site with personally identifiable information, Incentive Logic will delete that personally identifiable information.

**Internet-Related Information Gathered Passively**

We collect Internet-related Information from visitors to our Site, including the referring URL, your IP address, which browser you used to come to the Site, the country, state or province, the pages of our Site that you viewed during your visit and any search terms entered on our Site, for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, and to monitor the level of activity on our Site. We track visitors’ traffic patterns throughout their online sessions, including which pages or specific URLs a customer views while using the Site. We use your Internet-related Information to diagnose problems with our servers and software and to administer our Site. We may share aggregated statistics about pages viewed on our Site, demographic information and sales and other browsing information with third parties to enrich your visitor experience.

**Cookies**

When you visit this Site, we leave a "Cookie" in the memory of your Web browser. We, and our third party web analytics service providers, use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Cookies cannot access or read the files on your hard drive and cannot be used as a virus. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse Cookies. However, by doing so you may not be able to access some features of the Site. The use of cookies by our web analytics service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

Our third party traffic analyzer partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

**Actively Collected Personal Information You Provide**

If you provide information about yourself (such as your name, email address, physical address and company name) by registering on a page, participating in any activities on the Site, or otherwise voluntarily telling us about yourself or your activities, we will collect and use that Personal Information to respond to your request, and for other business purposes, including, without limitation, identifying consumer preferences, and improving our products and services and the content of this Site.

We may also contact you by email, regular mail, fax, or telephone from time to time with information about our new products and services, special offers, upcoming events and changes to this Site. If you do not wish to be contacted by all or any of these methods, you may let us know by contacting us through one of the ways listed under the Contact Us section. Please be sure to give us your exact name and address, and your detailed request so we can respond appropriately.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us through one of the methods listed below. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Sharing Information**

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as sending service related emails on our behalf. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties for their promotional purposes.

Incentive Logic also reserves the right to disclose and transfer user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, financing, the sale of substantially all assets, or other corporate change. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

**Links To Other Websites**

On this Site, we may provide as a convenience to you links to other websites, including sites operated by us, our partners, associates, or independent third parties. Each website has its own privacy practices, as described in that site's privacy policy. Those practices may be different than the practices described herein, and we urge you to read each website's privacy policy carefully before you use or submit information to that site. Additionally, to the extent that you follow a link to a website operated by an independent third party, please be aware that we exercise no authority or control over that third party, and cannot and are not responsible for any information that you may submit at that site.

**Testimonials**

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you would like to request the removal of your testimonial, please contact us through one of the methods listed below.

**Where Do We Store And How Do We Secure Your Personal Information**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure your Personal Information is kept in a physically and technologically secure environment and accessed only by authorized personnel or contractors who are bound to keep your information confidential. We have in place procedures for training our employees about their obligations under this Privacy Policy, disciplining them for failure to follow this Policy. We also have in place internal procedures to confirm general company compliance with this Policy. Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of any Personal Information collected, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security, and we will not be liable for disclosure of Personal Information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.

**Access to Your Information**

Upon request, Incentive Logic will grant individuals reasonable access to Personal Information that it holds about them based on the information collected by individuals submitted by them at our Site. In addition, Incentive Logic will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. To make this request, please contact us through one of the methods listed below. Incentive Logic will respond to this request within 30 days.

**Acceptance and Changes**

By using this Site, you accept the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our use of your Personal Information you may contact our Customer Service department by email at [info@incentivelogic.com](mailto:info@incentivelogic.com), or by using the [Contact Us](http://www.incentivelogic.com/contact-us) form or via standard mail at Incentive Logic, Inc., 7600 E. Redfield Dr. Suite #140, Scottsdale, AZ 85260.
